field-by.com 2011-05-24

# Privacy Policy | FiledBy

Updated: September 08, 2010

FiledBy, Inc. ("FiledBy",or "We") respects the privacy of individuals who visit our website, [http://www.filedby.com](http://www.filedby.com/), and is committed to protecting your online personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

While you can use many features of our website without being required to provide personally identifiable information, you may be requested to provide your personal information to gain access to some of our content or services, to contact us, or to receive additional information from us. By visiting [http://www.filedby.com](http://www.filedby.com/), you accept and agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

This statement describes:  
Who we are.  
What information we collect and how the information is collected.  
How we use and protect the information we collect.  
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information.  
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

#### FiledBy

FiledBy is a company specializing in providing digital media and marketing services to authors and content developers and access to such by consumers.

Information We Collect. We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to others in ways different from what is disclosed within this statement and within any agreements with our customers.

We may collect personal information about you when you visit [www.filedby.com](http://www.filedby.com/), which may give you the ability to access additional features on our website and our online services. This information is used to provide you with the information that you are requesting from us, access to our services and Authorized Content Distribution Partners and data and information regarding the services we provide to you. Personal information we collect may include your: login ID and password, name, company name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, fax number and additional information used to contact you.

We may also collect automatic information about your visit to our website, such as time of day, browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. This information is used for analytical purposes and to help us provide services to our members. We may also use this information to administer and troubleshoot the www.filedby.com website.

#### Use of Personal Information

We use information collected regarding visitors to our website only as appropriate to provide authorized services or to communicate information regarding our services. No information regarding specific persons, including our customers, our employees, or visitors to our website, will be provided to any non-affiliated organization, except as may be legally required, to prevent fraud, or to comply with the legal inquiry of the government. This policy does not preclude our unrestricted use of non-personal, summarized, derived, or aggregate information (i.e., volumes, totals, averages, etc.). Please be aware that if you submit personal information as a public posting or comment, your information may become widely available to other users. FiledBy cannot control or be responsible for personal information, which you choose to make public.

#### Customer Options

We do not anticipate a change in our policies regarding the use of personal information (see previous section "Use of Personal Information"). However, should we, at some future time, change our practices regarding the use of personal information (i.e., to share such information with third parties) we will provide notice by posting it on our website.

#### Changes to Information Security and Privacy Statement

We continue to adhere to good business practices. We will regularly review our policies and practices as we believe is warranted. Changes that are made that affect our Privacy Policy will be posted to our website.

#### Protection of Personal Information

We have taken precautions to protect your personal information under our control from misuse, loss or alteration. Our security measures include industry standard technology and equipment to help protect your data. Unfortunately, however, no system can ensure complete security and you should take all necessary steps to protect your information and its transmission to us. Since the Internet is a public medium, we cannot guarantee the absolute protection of your personal information.

#### What We Provide to Third-Parties

Authorized third-party agents may need access to some of your personal information. In such cases, we only provide authorized third-party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We may also provide your information to our affiliated companies and successors.

We also reserve the right to provide authorized third-parties with aggregate statistics about our clients, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data may reflect site usage patterns and other information.

#### Public Author Page Information Sharing

FiledBy has entered into agreements with selected third parties such as Ingram Content Group and Copa (DMC Worldwide)(out "Authorized Content Distribution Partners"). Under these agreements, FiledBy receives and shares publicly available author, publication and similar information. The intent of these relationships is to help authors registered at FiledBy to market themselves and their work more broadly on the Internet. By posting or correcting information about works that you have created or about yourself on a publicly available author page on www.filedby.com, you agree that we may allow our Authorized Content Distribution Partners to access, use and display such information for the purpose of additional author promotion and to improve the accuracy of author information. By way of example, FiledBy provides corrected author and book information to Ingram Content Group to assist in pudating incorrect or out of date information in the Ingram databases, which are used by booksellers everywhere. FiledBy also serves publicly available author information to other Authored Content Distribution Partners, such as Copia, a website that promotes authors and sells books and ebooks.

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that some websites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other websites, we may use cookies to identify users for our business purposes.

#### IP Addresses

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer for accessing the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted using IP addresses to allow other computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. If a visitor requests pages from the FiledBy site(s) or our affiliate site(s), the servers enter the visitor's IP address into a log. We do not associate IP addresses with personal information received from visitors.

#### External Links

We may provide links to third-party websites or enable links to be posted by users. Because we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites or the information collected on such websites.

#### Obtaining Your Consent

By using our website, you authorize us to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user. This information will be used for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register as a user of our website, you authorize us to personalize the information that we deliver to you and to use your information when calculating aggregate client data. As a registered site user, you give us and our agents permission to send you e-mails or place phone calls to you.

#### Opt Out

We respect your privacy and ability to choose whether to share private information with any third-party and us. You may choose not to share private information in several ways. When choosing to use certain features or services on the website, you may choose not to share optional private information in connection with the feature or service. Your user name provided as part of your Login will not be considered private; however, you may choose to keep other information about yourself private through the management features of your account. Be aware that if you post your own private information to a public page on the www.filedby.com website, it will become permanently and publicly available. We advise considering whether or not to publicly post your private information very carefully. If you receive communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt out from receiving these communications by specifically indicating this preference in a communication to us sent to: [info@filedby.com](mailto:http://www.filedby.com). You may also "opt-out" from providing personal information to us by not registering as an authorized user on the website and thereby not providing personal information.

The book and author information displayed on our website is provided directly from publishers or trusted, licensed bibliographic sources. FiledBy provides Creators with tools to update and correct their bibliographic data on the Site, but does not delete data from the site.

#### Children

We do not provide services to children. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.

#### Compliance with Legal Process

Please be aware that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We may also choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, but are not under any obligation to do so. 

#### California Privacy

The California Civil Code, Section 1798.83 permits individuals who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [info@filedby.com](mailto:http://www.filedby.com).

#### Canada Privacy

Canadian residents have the right to know how their information may be shared with third parties who engage in direct marketing activities. FiledBy's policies are set forth in this document. To make a specific request or inquiry, please send an e-mail to [info@filedby.com](mailto:http://www.filedby.com).

#### Your Responsibility

As a user/customer/merchant to one of our websites, you may be provided with a unique identifier such as a password or pin number which is intended to authenticate your identity when accessing our systems. Such identifying items are intended to be secret and to be known, possessed, and used only by you. The effectiveness of these mechanisms for authenticating your identity are dependent upon your keeping them in your exclusive possession and upon your protecting them from the discovery, access, and possession of others. If you fail to keep such identifying information in your exclusive possession (i.e., you allow others to have knowledge or possession of your password or pin), you may bear responsibility for the actions of other persons who use this information in accessing our systems. If your personal identifier pin number has been lost or disclosed to someone other than yourself, you should immediately contact customer service.

#### Digital Millennium Copyright Act

FiledBy takes allegations of infringement seriously. FiledBy reserves the right to remove any material or suspend the account of any user. If you believe that one of your works has been copied, infringed or violated, you should notify FiledBy by providing the following information: (i) a description of the work you own or control; (ii) a description of the allegedly infringing material and its location on the Site; (iii) your address, telephone number, and email address; (iv) your statement that you have a good faith belief that the use is infringing and not authorized; (v) and the following statement: "Under penalty of perjury, I have the authority to submit this notice on my behalf or on behalf of the copyright owner, the statements made in this notice are true and accurate, and I am not submitting this notice for any malicious purpose." The notice must be signed by you. Pursuant to Title 17, U.S.C. §512(c)(2), notifications of claimed copyright infringement must be sent to FiledBy's Designated Agent. FiledBy's Designated Agent will receive notices addressed as follows: DMCA Notices -FiledBy, Inc. at [info[at]filedby[dot]com](mailto:info@filedby.com) or by fax at (615) 712-8918. Your notice may not be submitted by email.

#### Policy Updates

We may change this privacy policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any updates to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Continued use of the website following our posting of the change notice or an updated privacy policy will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
